My memories awaken within this blue forest
The beast in my chest, sneering in the darkness
In the contest of wills, one in white who stays by my side
Bring forth the light, satisfy my thirst
Reflected in these eyes is the heat of a distant summer day
Shaded in the sky is the blood over the moonlight
Transcending the far reaches of time is my love for your soul
I'll never let go of this night
In the dead of night, the heat haze from distant days
Surfaces weakly in the crimson moonlight
The one in white, who silently falls down
Bring forth the light, satisfy my thirst
As if sweetly melting, the faint scent of blood draws me in
announcing the demise of my peaceful daily life
In the awoken memories, something has emerged far in the distance
In the moments which are passed down...
In the contest of wills, one in white who stays by my side
Bring forth the light, satisfy my thirst
Reflected in these eyes is the heat of a distant summer day
Shaded in the sky is the blood over the moonlight
Transcending the far reaches of time is my love for your soul
I'll never let go of this night